&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：同样，请遵循幻灯片上的代码。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So again, follow along with that code on the slide.
我将为你们绘制图表，我们将逐行进行
And I'm gonna be diagramming it for you and we're gonna go line by line and
创建实体。
create the entities.
在我们到达一号线之前，
Before we even get to line one,
我们需要画出一些零行发生的事情，换句话说，
we need to diagram a bit about what's happening in line zero, in other words,
在你的程序开始运行之前发生了什么。
what's happening before your program has even started to run.
在这个图表中，我将使用一个非常简单的符号，即我将
And in this diagramming I'm gonna use a very simple notation which is I'm gonna
使用正方形表示对象和圆或
use squares to represent objects and circles or
只要我能近似它来表示函数。
whatever I can approximate thereof to represent functions.
我正在用触控板画，所以
I am drawing with a trackpad so
这不会是伟大的绘画，请原谅我的艺术作品的质量。
it's not gonna be great drawing please forgive the quality of my artwork.
我首先要画出零环境线，我要这样做
I'm going to diagram first the lines zero environment i'm going to do that by
在这里划一条线，基本上就是说这条线以上的所有东西都是
drawing a line across here that basically says everything above this line is
零线环境，然后下面是我们要绘制程序图的地方。
the line zero environment, and then below it is where we'll diagram the program.
在我们的零线环境中，
Above this line in our line zero environment,
有一个非常关键的实体。
there's one very critical entity.
它是一个函数，所以我将它画成一个近似的圆
It is a function, so I will draw it as approximately a circle and
它有一个非常熟悉的名字，它的名字是大写O，Object。
it goes by a pretty familiar name, it goes by the name capital O, object.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我只是缩写，因为我不喜欢写出来
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I'm just gonna abbreviate cuz I don't like writing out
这整个单词，但它被称为对象，大写O对象和
this whole words, but it's called object, capital O object and
这是一个存在的函数。
that's a function that exists.
你们都看到了这是我们的基本目标之一
And you all have seen that that's one of our fundamental objects
这是语言中内置的，可能是其中最重要的一个。
that's built into the language, probably one of the most important of those.
我们有大写的O对象，顺便说一下，它上面有几个东西。
We have capital O object there, and by the way, it has several things on it.
它有object.key和object.values以及各种其他实用程序。
It's got object.keys and object.values, and various other utilities.
所以它不仅是一个函数，而且
So it's not only a function, but
它还可以用作名称空间，以便在其上使用其他方法。
it also serves as a namespace to have other methods on it.
所以有一堆我们使用的非常重要的通用工具
So there are a bunch of really important general utilities that we use
在整个JavaScript中，它们直接位于该函数上。
across JavaScript, that are located directly on that function.
但还有另一个存在的实体，它是一个正方形。
But there's another entity that exists and it is a square.
所以我将在这里画一个正方形，类似于正方形。
So I will draw a square here, something like a square.
它可能是所有JavaScript中最重要的对象。
And it is probably the most important object in all of JavaScript.
它是如此重要，事实上，我们甚至没有它的名字。
It's so important in fact that we don't even have a name for it.
我们不能给它起个好名字。
We can't come up with a good name for it.
所以你知道我们怎么命名它，是不是我们命名它指的是它所指的点。
So you know how we name it, is we name it referring to what points at it.
对象函数上有一个属性指向
There's a property on the object function that points
在这个东西上，那个属性叫做原型。
over at this thing and that property is called prototype.
在这里写作真的很痛苦。
Writing is really painful here.
我只是在这里用Proto缩写。
I'm just gonna abbreviate with proto here.
这叫原型。
It's called prototype.
这是该属性的名称。
That is the name of that property.
因此，如果您曾经看到过object.prototype，那就是指向
So if you've ever seen object.prototype, that's the property pointing from
对象函数转移到一个名为object.prototype的东西上。
the object function over to this thing called object.prototype.
在对象上有一堆非常重要的东西。原型，
And there's a bunch of really important stuff on object.prototype,
像toString、valueOf和
like toString, and valueOf, and
所有这些存在于我们语言中的基本工具。
all these other fundamental utilities that exist in our language.
所有非原语都是直接从这个对象派生出来的。Prototype，所以
All non-primitives descend directly from this object.prototype, so
这是一个非常重要的物品。
it's a really important object.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在我们的零线环境中还有一件事
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There is one other thing that exists in our line zero environment
这是一个指向另一个方向的属性。
which is a property that's pointing back the other direction.
它从这里指向这里
It's pointing from here over to here and
他们为这个财产选择了一个令人费解和令人沮丧的名字。
that property they chose a really perplexing and frustrating name for.
他们选择一个特定的名字，因为他们试图做的事情本质上是谎言
They choose a specific name because what they were trying to do was essentially lie
对你来说，假装JavaScript系统有类
to you, to pretend as if JavaScript system had classes so
他们选择命名这个构造函数。
they choose to name this constructor.
我只想写c-o-n来缩写。
And I'm just going to write c-o-n to abbreviate.
这叫做构造函数。
It's called constructor.
所以你有这个object.prototype，它指向这个对象，并且
So you have this object.prototype which points at this object, and
如果您有该对象，然后说.structor，
if you had that object and then said .constructor,
它会指向这个对象函数，就好像对象
it'd be pointing back at this object function as if the object
函数是指向它的对象的构造函数。
function was the constructor of the object that pointed to it.
但是基本原型中工作构造函数
But that work constructor in the fundamental prototype
系统没有比单词fubar更多的含义。
system has no more meaning than the word fubar.
除了说服你
Other than to convince you,
这是一个类系统，因为它包含构造函数，我们将看到一些
that this is a class system because it has constructors in it and we will see a bit
稍后，这就是构造函数基本上进入并假装它，
later that's what constructor basically comes in and pretends it,
如果你愿意的话，这有助于技巧，我们正在处理的是一个阶级系统。
it helps the artifice if you will, that we are dealing with a class system.
所以我们的零线环境。
So that our line zero environment.
现在我要用同样的符号重新开始绘制图表，但是
Now I'm gonna start diagraming again with the same notation but
我从一号线开始。
I'm gonna start with line one.
在一号线，我们有一个车间功能，
On line one, we have a workshop function,
我是不是要画一个圆圈，这叫做工作坊。
do I'm gonna draw a circle and it's called workshop.
但我只想缩写w代表工作坊。
But I'm just gonna abbreviate w for workshop.
这是存在于第一行的函数。
That's the function that exists on line one.
但也存在于一号线上，这并不明显，
But also what exists on line one, that is not obvious,
是存在另一个对象，该对象是作为第一行的结果而创建的，并且
is that there is another object that has been created as a result of line one and
那个对象也是相当重要的。
that object is also pretty important.
目前它是空的，但它将起到非常重要的作用
At the moment it's empty but it's gonna serve a pretty important purpose
只是它太重要了，我们没有一个好的名字。
except it's so important that we don't have a good name for it.
因此我们通过指向它的属性来引用它。
And so we refer to it by the property that points at it.
我打赌你能猜到那房子叫什么？
And I bet you can guess what that property's called?
那个财产叫Proto，Prototype，好吗？
That property's called proto, prototype, okay?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我可能正在使用文本工具，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I could probably be using the text tool,
但我只是不想在工具之间切换。
but I just didn't wanna mess around with switching between tools.
这就是所谓的原型。
So that's called prototype.
因此我们将该对象称为workshop.prototype，
So we refer to that object as workshop.prototype,
这就是你在第四行看到的，Workshop.Prototype。
which is what you see on line four, workshop.prototype.
这是一个奇怪的名字，比如Prototype到底是从哪里来的？
It's a bizarrely named word like where does prototype even come from?
我试图在计算机科学中寻找原型的起源，并且
I've tried to search for the origins of prototype within computer science, and
这充其量是一个模糊的词源。
it's a murky etymology at best.
我想不出为什么我们用这个词Prototype或者
I can't come up with why we use this word prototype or
它到底是什么意思。
what it's even supposed to mean.
但在这条线上还有另外一件事，
But there is one other thing that exist on this line one,
这就是从这里回到这里有一个联系，
which is that there is a linkage from here back to here,
有一个属性指向后，该属性也称为构造函数。
there is a property pointing back, and that one is also called constructor.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：再一次，它们的存在只是为了试图假装
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And again, that exist only for the purpose of trying to pretend
对于您来说，该对象是由车间功能创建的，
to you that, that object was created by the workshop function,
就好像车间函数是类的构造函数一样。
as if the workshop function is a constructor for classes.
最后一个存在的东西，是一种隐藏的关系
And one final thing that exists, there is a hidden relationship
在这个物体和这个物体之间。
between this object and this object.
如果可以的话，我会用虚线来做。
I'm gonna do it, if I can, with a dotted line.
这两个人之间有一种隐藏的关系。
There's a hidden relationship between those two.
我们稍后再谈这段关系。
We'll come back to that relationship later.
但所有这些都是一号线的结果。
But all that's a result of line one.
你听懂了吗？
You follow me?
好的，让我们转到四号线。
All right, let's move to line four.
我们稍后会回到两个。
We'll come back to two later.
让我们转到四号线。
Let's move to line four.
在第四行，我们创建一个属性并将其添加到workshop.prototype。
On line four, we make a property and add it to workshop.prototype.
在这种情况下，它是一个函数并不重要。
It doesn't matter that it's a function at this case.
所以我真的要把它写进去。
So I'm just gonna literally write it in.
我们只是将名为ask的属性直接添加到此对象。
We're just adding a property called ask directly to this object.
你和我一起吗？
You with me?
这就是第四行所做的。
That's what line four does.
我们跳到八号线。
We'll skip down to line eight.
这才是真正有趣的地方。
That's what's really interesting.
我想回顾一下，如果你想拉出一张幻灯片或者
And I wanna review, if you wanna pull up a slide or
翻回你的幻灯片，无论何时都会发生四件事
flip back in your slides, there were four things that happened whenever
new运算符被放在函数调用的前面，就像它在第八行中的方式一样。
the new operator was put in front of a function call the way it is on line eight.
现在我们想要做这四件事，我将把它们每一件都画成图表。
Now we want to do those four things and I'm gonna diagram each one of them.
所以第一，当新的东西被放在前面时发生的第一件事
So number one, the first thing that happens when new is put in front of
一个函数调用是，它凭空创建了一个全新的空对象。
a function call is that it creates a brand new empty object out of thin air.
所以这就是我的全新的空虚物体。
So here is my brand new empty object out of thin air.
然后它将该对象链接到另一个对象。
And then it links that object to another object.
所以在这里我要做一个链接，
So here I'm gonna do a linkage,
这个隐藏的小链接与虚线。
this little hidden linkage with the dotted line.
它将该对象链接到另一个对象。
It links that object to another object.
三号。
Number three.
它调用它前面被调用的函数。
It invokes the function that it was called in front of.
它用this关键字指向对象来调用它。
It invokes that with the this keyword pointing at the object.
所以我们到了，现在，我要移到二号线，然后
So here we are, now, I'm gonna move to line two, and
this关键字指向这个特定的对象，它做什么？
the this keyword is pointing at this particular object, and what does it do?
它添加了一个名为Teacher的属性，所以我们将把Teacher
It adds a property called teacher, so we're gonna put teacher
就在这里，我将用t-e-a缩写它。
directly right here on it, and I'm just gonna abbreviate that with t-e-a.
我们把老师直接放在那个物体上。
We put teacher directly on that object.
二号线就是这么做的。
That's what line two does.
大家都跟着我吗？
Everybody following me?
现在new关键字做的第四个也是最后一个，当它返回它时，
Now the fourth and final that the new keyword does, when it returns it back,
如果函数没有返回对象(在本例中没有)，
if the function does not return an object, which in this case it does not,
new关键字假设您的意思是返回this关键字，that brand
the new keyword assumes that you meant to return to the this keyword, that brand
新创建的对象，以便返回，并将其命名为Deep JS。
new created object so that's get returned back and it gets named deepJS.
因此，这个对象称为Deep JS。
So this object is called deepJS.
我会叫它深沉的。
I'll call it deep.
这就是第八行发生的事情，如果你知道行发生了什么
That's what happened with line eight and if you understand what happened with line
同样的事情发生在第九行。
eight the exact same thing happens with line nine.
所以我会简单地把它画进去。
So I'll simply draw it in.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我的画越来越差了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: My drawing is getting much worse.
然后它将教师属性添加到它上，然后它回来
And then it gets the teacher property added on to it and it comes back and
在这种情况下叫做反应JS。
it's called in this case reactJS.
所以我只说R-e代表反应JS。
So I'll just say R-e for reactJS.
这是第九行对象。
That's that object from line nine.
每个人都知道这些实体是从哪里来的
Everybody understand where these entities are coming from and
他们的关系是什么？
what their relationships are?
好的，让我们看看第11行。
Okay, so let's look at line 11.
在该代码片段的第11行，我们说Deep JS.ask。
On line 11 of that code snippet, we say deepJS.ask.
Deep JS对象，这里的这个对象，它有一个ask方法吗？
Does the deepJS object, this object right here, does it have an ask method?
不是的。
It does not.
那么为什么我们能够调用那个方法呢？
So why is it that we're able to call that method?
因为如果我们把这些看作是类，我们的心智模型
Because our mental model if we were thinking about these as classes
Ask方法将被复制到实例，但它不在那里。
is that the ask method would have been copied to the instance but it isn't there.
相反，将会发生的是内部链接，称为
Instead, what is gonna happen is that internal linkage, which is called
原型链，在SPECK中，他们使用括号，括号原型。
the prototype chain, in Speck, they use bracket, bracket prototype.
它被称为原型链，因此在内部有一个来自
It's called the prototype chain, and so internally there's a linkage from
深层物体，这个就在这里，一直到这个物体。
the deep object, this one right here, up to this object.
所以当我们在一个对象上寻找一个属性并且
So when we look for a property on an object and
它不存在，默认情况下，我们所做的就是做。
it doesn't exist, by default, what we do is do do do do do do do.
我们向上走一层到链中的下一个对象
We walk up one level to the next object in the chain and
我们问它有没有那个财产。
we ask if it has that property.
在这种情况下，确实是这样。
Which in this case, it does.
它有一个Ask方法。
It has an ask method.
当我们调用ask方法(本质上是第五行)时，
When we invoke the ask method, which was line five essentially,
this关键字将指向什么？
what is the this keyword gonna point at?
this关键字将指向哪个对象？
Which object is the this keyword gonna point at?
它会指向这个物体。
It's gonna point at this object.
为什么？
Why?
因为呼叫地点是11号线。
Because the call site is line 11.
调用站点表示在Deep JS的上下文中调用该函数。
The call site says invoke that function in the context of deepJS.
我们从哪里找到函数并不重要。
It doesn't matter where we find the function from.
在这种情况下，我们在原型链上找到了它，但这并不重要，
In this case, we found it up the prototype chain, but it doesn't matter,
我们仍然使用调用站点来调用它。
we still use the call site to invoke it.
您不习惯对JavaScript的管道进行如此深入的思考。
You're not used to generally thinking this deep about the plumbing of JavaScript.
但我认为重要的是，不要有不正确的思维模式。
But I think it's important, critical that you not have incorrect models of thinking.
好吧。所以如果我们可以这么说的话，
All right. So if we can say that with deepJS,
我们也可以用React对象来说。
we can also say that with the react object.
行14上的React对象当我们说.ask时，会发生完全相同的事情。
The react object on line 14 when we say .ask, the exact same thing happens.
我们没有问的方法，但我们去做。
We don't have an ask method but we go do do do do do do.
我们在调用ask方法时发现，正是这个关键字指出了我们的
We find the ask method when it is invoked, it's this keyword is pointing out our
对象，所以当它说这个，老师，它正在访问哪个属性？
object so when it says this .teacher which property is it accessing?
就在这里。
This one right here.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这真是太棒了，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's awesome right?
我们能够与潜在的无限数量的方法共享一种方法
We're able to share one method with potentially an infinite number of
实例，它们都能够共享它，因为这个绑定行为和
instances and they're all able to share it because of the this binding behavior and
那个原型链接。
that prototype linkage.
这实际上是一个非常棒的系统。
It's actually a really awesome system.
我根本不是说原型或者
I'm not at all saying that the prototype or
this关键字系统不好，我只是说可能有点太
the this keyword system is bad, I'm only saying that maybe it's a little too
限制只能通过类的镜头来思考这个问题。
limiting to try to think about this only through the lens of classes.
也许系统实际上比类设计模式更强大。
Maybe the system is actually much more powerful than the class design pattern.
如果你切换到下一张幻灯片，你会看到建筑物的示意图。
If you switch to your next slide you'll see the diagram of the buildings.
我现在要切换回幻灯片，所以
And I'm gonna switch back to the slides now, so
如果你想复制下来或不复制下来，没关系，我的小坏画。
if you wanna copy this down or not copy it down that's okay, my little bad drawing.
但现在至少你明白了一些基本行为的来龙去脉
But now at least you understand where some of those fundamental behaviors are coming
这些关系来自于。
from, those relationships are coming from.